I bet you didn't expect to wake up today
with advice that you need to steal,
because I don't think you truly realize
how much theft and
thieving I have done to get to the
position I'm in,
and it didn't used to be this
way. In this video,
I'm going to explain
and show you how to steal content ideas,
how to steal business ideas,
how to steal in general.
Because my theft counter, well,
it's just hit $100 million.
Because do you think I really came up with
the idea of Nootonic from nowhere?
Now, quickly to set this up,
I've got a bit of a confession to make.
And you would not expect to hear this come
out of my mouth.
There used to be a time that I
was too proud to steal,
and I thought stealing ideas
was bad. And there
was even a person called Adam Sullivan,
who is an Australian
personal trainer entrepreneur, and he
was stealing from me. My ideas, my videos.
I was getting sent them,
and my way of coping with that
was to block him.
And at the time, I thought it
was because I was trying to protect my
ideas, but
actually now, being a bit more mature
and older, I look back, I
was jealous of him.
Because he had taken my ideas
and done better with them than I could
ever have imagined.
He would've had some months where he
was making more money in a
four-week period than I
was making in a year,
and I didn't like that, so I decided
to block him. Then, a few years later,
we're speaking at the same event.
The guy running the event says, "Oi,
he's actually a good dude." Let me show
you
Adam quickly.
Adam grew up in a part of Sydney with not
a lot of money, and he's a
self-made multimillionaire,
and he's actually now one of my very good
friends.
Two things I've learned from Adam.
One,
he helped me be okay with buying nice
things and publicly
showing it off,
because I think I went through a period of
my life, because I'm
British,
where I didn't want to have nice things
because I thought people might
hate me for it.
And then only seeing Adam with his nice
things, I actually realized
the people that are your true OGs
that want to see you do well,
they want to see
you do well. And now I look at Adam
and all the things that he stole from me
idea-wise. I'm happy for him,
and I'm proud of him in some sense because
this is
how things work. Quite literally,
nothing is original.
If you're not looking
and monitoring as to what is doing well,
thinking of
doing it yourself,
you're not going to survive. Yesterday,
I put out a reel.
It's about Ronda Patrick being a fucking
idiot about the smoothie and banana
incident. Want to know how that happened?
Saw the reel.
Thought, "Oh,
that's stupid." Saw a reaction to it.
"Oh yeah,
that's stupid." Saw another reaction to
it, and I was like, "Hold on,
there's a pattern emerging.
It's time for me to jump on this trend."
What did I do?
I went and I looked at some of the
best-performing reels, created my own.
Boom.
Put it out. I thieved what
was already working.
Back to the $100 million idea.
Let me give you the raw,
unfiltered, honest truth about Nootonic.
Okay, let's go.
So this is modafinil. This
is a narcolepsy drug.
I used to take this all the time to help
me concentrate.
And I'll be honest with you,
I used this to write not one, not two,
but three "Sunday Times" number one
best-selling books.
2020, 2021, 2022.
I will take any pill that helps me
concentrate, lock in. And this
was before they became fairly
mainstream. And I
was well aware of products like Alpha
Brain by Joe Rogan.
Alpha Brain. Alpha Brain. Alpha Brain.
I'm pretty sure he exited to Unilever for
millions.
So straight away,
I knew the nootropic business
was pretty big.
I thought to myself,
"How could we make a legal modafinil to
take on
Alpha Brain?" So we started the
formulation process.
We liked Rhodiola rosea, cognizin,
citicoline, theanine, and Panax ginseng.
So we're formulating, trying things out,
looking at different territories.
Obviously, at this stage,
I'm mainly Australia, USA.
Then my manager is also working with Chris
Williamson.
He's looking into creating a nootropic
product. We get pulled together.
But one of my concerns in one of our
meetings was we've got a great
formulation,
we've got a great amount of pills.
What are we going to do?
Drink this with a fucking can of Ghost to
get it down? Where's the caffeine?
So it was only when we thought about this,
plus this, plus this,
that we came up with this.
So this wasn't an original idea.
It was a combination of other ideas. Sold,
made millions.
Sold, made billions.
So we're going into production.
We're doing well.
Probably sell like a million
or two million cans.
This was still rattling in the background.
So we thought, "Okay,
we've kind of stolen the idea.
We've kind of stolen the concept.
Why don't we steal it more?"
So we took the formulation then,
but for this,
we added two more nootropics.
It's called bacopa monnieri
and ginkgo biloba.
We are now directly competing with
that market with these,
which do incredibly
well. Then we've got the focus blends,
which are pretty much a mix of
everything. So then, about middle,
late last year,
whilst I'm writing book four,
what happens? Nicotine pouches.
And I'm taking them,
I'm having them with a can of
Nootonic.
And I don't quite like the idea of having
nicotine, but do
you know what? It's not even
that I like the ingredients.
It's that I like the product.
I liked having something in my lip.
I sat back and realized we've ripped off
everything else so far and made our own
product out of it.
Why don't we make a Better For You
nicotine pouch?
Now,
one of the advantages we have with this,
shipping.
Very light, so these come from the UK,
even to people in Australia.
The price, we can be very competitive.
These cost about £5 per pack.
We sell a five-pack for 25.
A lot of our competitors on TikTok sell
them for a lot
more than that.
We put 20 pouches per pack,
rather than a lot of our competitors do
15.
And there are other brands doing these,
but I've tried a lot of them, and I
think ours is better.
So you might have thought the level of
thieving and
stealing at that point would've been done,
but no.
Creatine enters the chat.
I have been pretty terrible with
taking creatine over the years.
Some of you will have seen
that we did that video
where we took down that company
that didn't have any creatine in it.
I was actually in the process of investing
into that business, and it was in the
due diligence phase
that everything kind of fell apart.
Because I had seen the paid ads.
They'd not seen the amount of orders
that are
happening on Amazon.
And then after the investment fell
through, for obvious
reasons,
I start investigating creatine gummy
market for
inspiration.
That means I want to steal the idea
and I want to do it
better. The mistake I made
was I took the owner of the gummy
company on a private jet to Ibiza for a
vendor.
But on that private jet
was one other dickhead called Adam
Sullivan.
So what did he do?
He beat me to market, the dog. But again,
I'm kind of proud of Adam.
He's made millions from this gummy idea,
which I put in his head
by putting him on the jet,
introducing him to the guy,
making millions from it.
The Rolex is coming.
Maybe it's just on a wait list somewhere.
If he's going to get me like a rose gold
Daytona or something, he's probably got to
wait a little bit of time. I'll be honest,
I'm happy for Adam.
I'm proud of Adam for what he's done with
the gummies.
For me, going through the process,
I get a bit of stomach upset
if I have too many
of them. So then we think, "Okay,
how can we not just compete with this
market?"
Because I do think I've knocked buyer
and consumer confidence with the gummies,
but
I still want to compete there.
Now we're going for the giant bags.
Just not going to go. So the avenue
that we believe, and actually is working,
is we're going for
that creatine convenience
So each sachet is 5 grams.
They're flavored, you mix them with water,
and the idea
is that having them as a travel pack
is going to be where we can separate
ourselves
from the competition. If you had these
and you're going abroad for seven days or
traveling,
you would have to get the gummies,
put them into something, and take
them with you. Whereas with these sticks,
when I travel, it's like, how many days
am I going to be away for?
And I just stick the sticks in.
Now, again,
are we the first people to do sachet
sticks? Absolutely not.
Even when it came to ordering the
quantities for those that we needed,
we went onto
Amazon and to other websites
and looked at other companies that
are currently
crushing in those realms.
Then we look at their creatives,
we look at their copy,
we look at what's working for them.
Because when it comes to thieving ideas,
there's been a lot of testing that's
already occurred. So for instance,
if you're going to go to a platform
that are
selling the thing you're selling,
there's going to be a few hints on the
page.
Which product is the first that they show?
Is it the ready-to-drink?
Is it the capsules? Is it the powders?
What are the price points?
What are the subscription offers?
Sometimes by going to a competitor's
landing page or lead magnet or whatever,
there
could be five years of testing
that they've done to optimize
that process.
And if you go in and just take inspiration
from it, you're skipping all of those
years of trial and error.
I can openly stand here proudly
and admit that since I
stopped caring so much about all of my
ideas being original and being open to
the fact that I do now take inspiration
from good things and try and do them
better, I've done a lot better in life.
Because let's be honest, even
if you think that I'm an evil capitalist
pig, the
only reason that I would be able to make
money across all of these products is
there is a consumer problem,
and I solve that problem.
And I do have nights where I'm a bit
insecure and I worry about stuff,
so I offer
100% money-back guarantee on everything I
sell.
So I know that every single dollar in the
bank account, which is millions now,
well, in the business bank account,
is a happy customer because if it wasn't,
I
would've sent them the money back,
which is great.
So we're on track to do $25 to $30 million
this year for Nutonic.
So that takes our valuation north of $100
million, which is amazing.
But I've still not been paid,
and I might not be for a few more years,
but it's fun
again. And guess what?
If I see anything on the landscape online
that even
[sniffs] smells like a good idea,
I'm going to steal it.
Let's get back into the other thefts.
Okay, so another place
that you want to be able to steal ideas
is when it
comes to videos.
Let's have a look down here.
This one really annoyed the guy
that originally did this video.
So he even cries about it in the comments.
I think he must just be new to YouTube.
If I go, "Unfortunately fitness really
is this simple," you'll see the
outlier here. It was just by a guy,
and I actually needed to just get some
leads
onto my training app.
I knew it'd get like 50,000 views.
Here you go.
He had a 21.7 times outlier,
so of course I was going to give
that a little bit of
theft. Average to jacked. Bro,
keep it up and all that. But where is he?
Oh, maybe he deleted his comment. Yeah,
he was in here like, "Bro, I really
didn't think it's okay.
You're stealing my title." I'm like,
"Mate,
relax. This is YouTube, brother." That
is quite literally what we want to do.
We want to find packaging because remember
what I said before, that so many
people have already done the trial
and error for the last however many
years to find things that work.
So once they've found a secret sauce, we
should go after that. So for instance,
this guy, Oscar Moves, at the moment, is
absolutely crushing in the mobility space.
Some of his videos
are going absolutely crazy.
Now if we go to videos
and maybe we go to popular,
already something I've just
noticed there was two months ago,
he did this video,
"Five mobility exercises
that fix 95% of your problems." 7.8 times
outlier, 3 million views.
If we go to latest,
have you noticed he's just recreated it 12
days later?
So he's copying himself down here again.
He's found a formula that's worked,
so two months ago, three months
ago, so he's getting it from himself.
Then again, you can see
that a lot of the things
that he's going from here.
You see this posture one here?
I know exactly where this has been stolen
from.
"Give me four minutes
and I'll fix your posture." This
is a Brian
Johnson,
even though I think he's a fucking gimp.
This is one of his because I know it's
probably his, maybe his most viewed
video. Ah, yes, told you, you
slag. Even there, hunched over, straight,
hunched over, straight.
YouTube is a place where this
is quite literally what you want to do,
is there's
frameworks that have gone well.
But then again, if we look at this one,
I already
know.
I think there's a Ryan Humiston outlier.
And by the way,
there's no prep to this video. This
is just the tism.
Ryan Humiston, by the way, great channel.
Love this guy.
Okay,
I would say it's maybe come from this one
here four years ago,
4.2 million views.
This video absolutely fucking crushed.
So you got like the squat mobility
masterclass, et cetera.
Then I believe Living Leggings might have
done a
version of this. Where is she? And this
is the level you have to get to on
YouTube. You've got to know.
You've got to know where people are.
There we go.
"This fixes everything." Three years ago,
603,000 views.
Ultimately, at the end of the day,
if something works, copy it.
Like the first car
that came out with a spoiler on the back.
Everyone else would go, "Oh my God,
what's that?" Then every car's got a
flipping
spoiler. Every single person
is copying each other.
This is actually part of like evolution
and the way that you progress.
This is why you need capitalism because
if you do not keep improving
and make stuff
better, someone else will come
and make it better.
Let's have a little look through here.
Let's see what else is coming up.
If you want to know as well,
here's a good one for kind of winning
formula.
So Carwow quite literally discovered a
formula for how to get
loads and loads of clicks on their videos.
So you'll notice all the Drag Race videos
look the same and have the same
format. A million views most of these get.
11 million subscribers.
But then if I type in Drag Race... Oh,
not that type of drag.
My God. Ugh, brother. Ugh, what's that,
brother?
That is not what I wanted.
What the hell has happened?
Carwow, Carwow, Carwow.
But I'm sure we get down
to other pages. Okay,
it's because I'm subscribed to Carwow,
innit?
Oh, there's another channel
that do these ones. Come on.
I wish there was a way to search not
Carwow. What's the other one?
Is it Full Throttle? Actually,
the way I know is they have a GT3
RS Turbo. Officially Gassed here we go.
So if you look at the Officially Gassed
channel here, you'll notice these look
exactly like Carwow. Why?
Because they worked for Carwow.
If they worked for Carwow,
if you don't steal it,
you're a fucking idiot.
Like you look at these thumbnails,
you think you could be looking at Carwow.
So again, they've got something
that works. They're going to copy it.
Or you never know,
Carwow could have copied Officially
Gassed.
Then if we look at the main OG guy to the
left here in a red T-shirt looking
at the camera, where's he got that from?
Matt Armstrong, 100%.
Matt Armstrong, bright T-shirt, front
and center looking at the camera.
You realize that these
are just all signals from the market.
Let's go M3 Repair, and then
probably going to find,
it's because I'm subscribed to the
channel.
There are other creators do similar kind
of things now because it worked for
Matt Armstrong, so they do it themselves.
This is the way things work.
If I want to go to Ed's channel.
I paid Ed 10 grand quite many
years ago.
He's now one of our main investors in
Nutonic, which is great.
Love that. But I'm getting everything I...
You know what I mean?
Then we look at some of his outliers here.
Three famous faces.
Actually,
I think I might need to go to Film Booth
because I've been stealing for a
while, brother.
See this one here where it says,
"I've read it." There was like
three famous people So then I ended up
making
this one up here,
where three famous people,
Down For The Moral Podcast, 1.2
million. Don't worry about it, brother.
All right,
so let me show you some other ones
that I've stolen.
And again, when I use the word steal,
I'm saying loosely. Loosely.
I really should use this channel more.
This AG one thumb,
stole off a dude with a ponytail,
and he had the green tash,
so I was like, "Look, that looked good,
brother,
so I'm nicking it." That's why the
bag is open.
This one got stolen off me a lot,
pretending to snort the
cocaine. Surely. Yeah,
that's the one I stole off that guy.
He was really unhappy about that.
Pathetic. Oh,
that's the time I met Hasbulla.
You ever met Hasbulla?
It's why we're different.
So the idea is, we
are to look for things that
are good ideas.
So Dr. Karan, if you're watching this,
brother, I don't like that Brian
Johnson is in your thumbnail twice.
Does my... I just don't like it.
We are looking for good ideas,
good titles. This one here.
How fast can black belt Tim Welch sub us?
Did okay.
I quite like the idea of the title.
Going to keep going down here.
Let's have a look.
So this one's quite an interesting one.
It only takes two weeks.
So the reason that I like this
is it's building a lot of curiosity.
What only takes two weeks?
And the fact it's got 5 million views,
the fact he's
doing 872 views per hour.
It only takes two weeks.
I could get a document up
and I could say to myself, "Title.
It only takes two weeks. It only takes
two months. It only takes two years." Then
I might say something like,
"It only takes 50
attempts. It only takes 23
days. It only take..."
And I'm just thinking of ideas here. "...
only takes one year. It only takes
one full day." So I'm just throwing some
things down here.
Then basically I want to think about an
idea or a concept that I'm trying
to flesh out. So for instance,
I'm about to revamp my Short-Form Content
Mastery
2.0. Any of you that buy that
or have bought it,
it's going to change in the next
week because the landscape of short-form
content has changed.
By the way, that'll be the end card video.
So don't jump away yet.
I'll send you there in a bit.
Then basically I would say, okay,
what am I selling?
So Short-Form Content Mastery 2.0.
So then I would look at these and go,
okay, it only takes 100 posts.
Then I would go, okay, what's my intro?
I would have to think about something here
and the introduction might say, "What if
I told you that you
are only 100 posts away from
being more confident,
getting better engagement, and winning
clients online every time you post?
The only thing between that goal and now
is 100 posts." Then I would go into some
kind of setup and be like, talk
about the issue,
the reason why they're not doing it,
or whatever.
But I'm kind of flagging through here.
I would then go back to this guy
and I would say, all right, this
is the idea or concept that I have. Guys,
what's that?
Oh, well,
if it isn't a document of another video
that we're currently stealing
from. I didn't actually steal that one.
That's my boy, Ollie. So.
Look at that. You only need 1,000 views.
That's close to the one we
were working on.
Do you want to know the truth?
I was here going through this thinking
about how we're going to do the video, and
I'll admit it, I got distracted
and I wanted to do a video about stealing
stuff
because that's my ADHD.
At the end of the day, thieving is okay.
I'm happy for Adam Sullivan.
I do often think what would happen to him
if I didn't
exist.
He'd probably be just a millionaire.
It's okay to go through
and look for ideas because they do it in
fashion. They do it in motorsport.
They do it in Formula 1.
Trends are the ways and the weaves
and the things that are moving between
people at any given point,
and we want to identify those so we can
ride the
wave. When we surf, we look at the sets,
we look at the waves.
When I surf,
I look to where everyone else is going.
I'll go over to that bit.
I'll wait for them to catch the wave
and I'll get the next one.
Ultimately, if I go out and try
and read the ocean,
it's going to be incredibly
difficult.
I'm better off looking at someone that's
been doing it for years longer
than me and following them, even
if I take the shitter wave.
That is the way that you can level up
and get ahead in life.
And you never know,
could make you $100 million, of which
I've had none,
so I'm actually a million in the hole.
So if you haven't tried New Tonic,
like I said, go to newtonic.com.
I'll put a link in the description.
But where I was saying about how
short-form content is changing,
I also stole that.
Think about this.
I have started using my phone to create a
lot of content
because I've seen other people doing it
and doing very well with it, and it's a
trend that I see, I believe in so much.
And I'm pretty sure you guys would've seen
the post I did yesterday.
Nearly a million views,
all edited from inside the edit site.
And my decision to go there wasn't my own.
I stole it off someone else.
So don't be afraid to steal. But
when you do steal, make sure that that
theft is channeled into the right medium,
whether it's product, whether
it's business, service, whatever it is.
If you're going to steal a video idea for
short-form content, it is
essential that you put it together right.
Which is why I made this video that I
was talking about earlier, which is how in
the last three months of 2026,
the short form content game landscape has
changed and it looks like it's going to
change forever.
I don't see it coming back from this.
So click this and you'll enjoy this one.